yoonla.com 2018-03-19

# Privacy Policy - Yoonla™

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested

In collecting and storing information, Yoonla.com will comply with the provisions of the Privacy Act 1993.

Yoonla.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of online marketing. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party.  Where any information held by us can be readily retrieved, you shall have access to it and the right to request correction.

**How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register to Yoonla.com or when you contact us. Or you might join one of our newsletters and provide your contact details then.

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualised content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Yoonla.com to communicate with you about your registration and customisation preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by Yoonla.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Yoonla.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Linked sites and advertisements**

Yoonla.com expects its partners to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Yoonla.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Yoonla.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Yoonla.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Yoonla.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Yoonla.com and this policy.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**

Yoonla.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 16 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 16 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Yoonla.com has any information from or about anyone under 16, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**

We can be contacted through our [support desk](http://support.yoonla.com/) or via the address below.

Postal Address:  
Yoonla™  
PO Box 1881  
Nelson 7040  
New Zealand

**Changes to this Policy**

Yoonla.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by New Zealand law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Nelson, New Zealand. Any costs and fees other than legal fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Nelson, New Zealand, under the rules of the province. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

Yoonla.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within New Zealand. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
